{"data":[{"question":"As the demand increases, manufacturers who previously produced only a large, luxury car is compelled to make a smaller model in order to compete in the market.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"As","b":"is","c":"to make","d":"to compete","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"The children were surprised when the teacher made them to close their books.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were surprised","b":"when","c":"made","d":"to close","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- To close->close","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"We were pleased to have the opportunity to watch such talented dancers to perform a highly new ballet.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were pleased","b":"to watch","c":"such talented","d":"to perform","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- To perform-> perform","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Your friend always is getting bad marks because he plays computer games too much.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"always is","b":"bad marks","c":"plays","d":"too much","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Always is-> is always","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Now that the newspaper arrived we can see the scores of the football match.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Now that","b":"arrived","c":"can see","d":"of","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Arrived-> arrives","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"We believe that she already feels very badly about her mistake.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"already feels","b":"badly","c":"about","d":"mistake","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Badly-> bad","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't see Jim since he moved to London.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"didn't see","b":"since","c":"moved","d":"to","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n-Didn't see-> haven't seen","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"For the first time in the history of the country, the person which was recommended by the president to replace a retiring justice on the Supreme Court is a woman.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"which","b":"to replace","c":"on","d":"is","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Which-> who","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Extreme patriots always believe that their country is better than any countries.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Extreme","b":"their","c":"better","d":"any","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- any-> other","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"In my opinion that girl is enough beautiful to be a movie star.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In my opinion","b":"enough","c":"to be","d":"star","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Enough beautiful-> beautiful enough","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"}]}